

# **MUHAMMAD RIZKI ADITYA**

+6281380564465 | muhammadrizkiaditya1@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/rizkidty/ | https://github.com/mrizkiaditya

Depok, Jawa Barat

Fresh graduate from Gunadarma University majoring in Informatics Engineering who has high enthusiasm and motivation in the field of Information Technology. Skilled in operating Microsoft Office, Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop and have a good understanding in HTML, CSS, PHP and MySQL. I have 1 year experience as Freelance Graphic Designer and have some projects in web development.

### **Education Level**

#### Gunadarma University - Depok, Indonesia

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science, 3.57/4.00

Jul 2018 - Sep 2022

Oct 2021 - Present

## Work Experiences & Projects

Freelance Graphic Designer

Kaldi.ld - Lampung

- · Created post and story designs, such as live music, food and beverage promos etc
- Created print designs, such as banner, voucher etc
- Created mock up designs

## Project Website for PT. Anugerah Bumi Samudra - Bogor

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023

Web Developer & UI/UX Designer

- · Designed UI/UX for user pages
- · Implemented front-end for website applications
- · Coordinated with team members to complete website applications

#### Project Website for Kaldi.ld - Lampung

Oct 2021 - Jan 2022

Web Developer

- Implemented front-end and back-end development for website applications
- Developed website applications using MySQL, HTML, CSS & PHP
- · Coordinated with team members to complete website applications

# **Organisational Experience**

English Club - Depok, Indonesia Member Oct 2016 - Apr 2017

## **Additional**

- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, JS, MySQL, ReactJS, PHP, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator
- Certification & Training: React JS Web Programming (Camp404, 2023), Occupation of Junior Web Programmer (Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi, 2022), Data Analyst (RevoU, 2022), Javascript Programming Language Fundamental (Gunadarma University, 2021), Java Course (Progate, 2021)
- Languages: Bahasa Indonesia, English